Come on in, Danny. Have a seat.
快进来呀，Danny.坐吧.
Thanks.
What's up?
有什么事吗?
I was wondering if you had a particular policy about animals in the apartment.
我不知道你对在公寓里养动物有没有什么特别的规定.
Animals? Like... bugs? Pests?
动物? 像臭虫一类的? 有害动物?
No, no. Pets.
No, no. 我说的是宠物.
Ahhh. Pets.
Ahhh. 宠物.
Yeah. See I think that if I got a pet,
Yeah. 你看，我要是养一只宠物的话，
it would help me focus on something other than myself and my petty problems.
就会有助于我把注意力集中在某些除我自己和一些小问题以外的什么事上.
It sounds like this is an important step for you.
听起来这对你好像是很重要的一步.
Also, this woman I'm seeing likes dogs.
再说，和我约会的这个女人很喜欢狗.
I see. Well, if you got a dog,
我懂了. Well, 如果你真要养狗的话，
we would have to agree on some conditions.
那我们得先谈好条件.
-For one thing, it couldn't be a puppy. -Oh.
-首先，不可以是小狗. -Oh.
Puppies are very tough on apartments,
小狗会把房间摘得乱七八糟的，
Danny. If you're not home when they need you,
Danny. 它们需要你的时候你要是不在家的话，
you will have all kinds of problems. Messes. Crying.
你会有各种各样的问题. 乱糟糟哪，叫声哪.
What about other animals?
那其他动物怎么样?
Can you narrow it down a little?
你能讲得具体点吗?
How would you feel if I got a monkey?
你感觉怎么样 如果我养一只猴子的话?
A monkey would not be OK.
养猴子是不行的.
A ferret?
那雪貂呢?
-No ferrets. -A boa constrictor.
-雪貂不行. -大蟒蛇.
I have a problem with wild animals, Danny.
野生动物对我来说都有问题，Danny.
If there's going to be a pet at all,
如果的确要养宠物的话，
it will have to be a domesticated one.
那也只能是驯化的宠物.
How about a fish?
你觉得养条鱼怎么样?
A fish sort of defeats the purpose of having a pet.
养鱼好像有点违背了我养宠物的初衷.
How so?
此话怎讲?
You can't pet a fish.
你又不能用手去爱抚一条鱼.